This is the time known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates go to battle across the seas in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure left behind by Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Hunky D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum gum fruit,
set sail to become the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the unwanted attention of the world government,
which will use any means necessary to stop them.
Stop this sight!
Can't wait to see what kind of adventure's up next!
With a charted course awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across the Grand Line to the New World.
After being separated from his crew, Luffy set out to rescue his captured brother Ace.
To do so, he snuck into the government prison, impelled down.
Bon Clay, who was saved by Ivankov of New Karma Land,
has just learned that Luffy's treatment against Warden Magellan's deadly poison has already begun.
Making miracles is never easy!
Believe in miracles!
Bon Clay's cries from the heart!
Miracle!
Nothing less.
And even then, it'll take a tremendous one for Straw Hat Boy to survive.
After everything he's been through, he's in rough shape.
You said it takes courage and spirit to make a miracle work,
and Straw Boy's got both!
I know he can do it!
He can do anything!
That's why I'm not nervous in the least!
Then practice what you preach and take a deep breath.
All we can do is wait and trust in him.
Uh-huh.
I ate the horn horn fruit!
It gave me the fabulous power to alter the hormones of anyone I see!
I can change their sex, body temperature, skin color, growth, even their emotions!
I can remodel people from the inside out, like an engineer of the human body!
The candy boys and candy girls you see here have used my help to really kick gender in its sorry pants!
Some men became women and some women men!
But all of those hang-ups are a thing of the past!
In short, those are the kind of miracles we deal in here!
I just provide the hormones!
Ha-ha!
Everyone else provides the dream!
Woo-hoo!
Oh, oh yeah!
He changed that man from earlier into a woman by injecting hormones!
Oh!
I still can't believe that there's a place like this in the middle of a prison!
I must be dreaming!
It's not a dream!
It's a dream land!
All of these candies you see around here were once lost prisoners who made it here by sheer luck, each with their own story!
See, there are hidden entrances to New Kamaland on every floor of Impel Down!
You just have to keep an eye out for them!
There's one at the Bloody Mountain of Needles, one in the Lair of Wild Beasts, one in the Burning Hellfire!
There's even one in the Mortuary!
We use these handy-dandy passages to go wherever we want in this prison to get everything we need!
A paradise hiding in the bowels of hell itself!
Why the jailers would never believe such an absurdity exists!
Despite living in our hidey-hole, we still keep tabs on everything that's going on outside!
We've got a line in one of the transponder snails, the very same ones the jailers use!
That way we're in on all the hip and horrible happenings here in the prison!
We also nab newspapers from the garbage so we can keep up with the other parts of the world!
And we were totally tuning in to Straw Hat Boy's Wild Ride!
It's not every day we get to see them break in, a break out, and all sorts of delectable nonsense!
We were cheering them on the whole way!
But it seems like this place of yours is gigantic!
Where exactly are we?
Oh, this place wasn't always here, I assure you!
Some prisoner had a devil fruit power that was good for digging!
They were the first to start chipping away at these caverns!
They led other prisoners here a long time ago, and bit by bit, the new recruits started building this place together!
To paint a picture, this paradise of ours is actually a bit like an ant farm made from digging tunnels in the rock!
But to answer your question specifically, we are located right in between Level 5 and Level 6!
Whoa! Hang on a minute! Did you say Level 6? I didn't know there was such a thing!
Well, it's not widely known, but I assure you it is there!
Level 6 is where the true villains are kept locked away!
Every one of them is condemned to a lifetime sentence without parole!
It's known as Eternal Hell!
Exceedingly wicked crimes are often covered up by the world government!
As are incidents that would tarnish the reputation of the powers that be!
You know, like your little rampage that took you all the way to Level 4!
If you had tried to pull that same maneuver a little while back, it wouldn't have been so easy, by the way!
There was another beastly baddie guarding this prison not too long ago, you see!
He was the jail manager of Impel Down, Shiryu of the Reign!
And to size him up, he was just as strong as Warden Magellan!
Honestly, considering that Magellan spends most of his time sitting on the crapper,
you might say Shiryu was twice as troublesome!
As strong as the Warden? Is that even possible?
Security's not too shabby these days, but when he was around, it was downright iron tight!
But you said he's gone now? What happened?
You said he's gone now, Shiryu, what do you think you're doing?
My job.
The prisoners aren't here for your amusement. I remind you that we're jailers, not butchers.
No one cares about the lives of these vermin.
I will not tolerate this any longer.
If someone were to find out about half the atrocities you've committed,
Impel Down would be disgraced beyond measure.
Now I must exercise my authority as Warden and place you under arrest.
He killed prisoners when and as he saw fit, even on the slightest whim.
He was completely out of control, so now they hold him in the darkest corners of level six
as a high-security risk.
Unbelievable! I've never heard of this!
I know it happened before I got here, but even so!
He's in fine company, too!
Catalina Davon, the world's most dangerous woman, is down there.
And San Juan Wolf, the great battleship.
Even heavy drinker Vosco Schott!
The names of these criminals are enough to make anyone tremble with fear!
It's the worst of the worst on level six.
Half the crimes these villains committed were so heinous, even the newspapers dared not mention them.
Your former boss is there, too.
I suppose he was pretty wild in his own way.
Mr. Zero? Crocodile?
Um, back in Alabaster, you had quite the little scuffle with Straw Hat Boy, didn't you?
And look at you now.
It just goes to show you that the power of friendship crosses all boundaries.
Reach it, friend!
Oh, and there's one of the warlords down there, the first son of the sea, Gene Ray.
Huh?
Along with that other guy, the one Straw Hat Boy came here to save.
Second Division Commander of the Whitebeard Pirates, the Fire Fist, Portgusty Ace.
I heard about it over the radio.
They're brothers, if I'm not mistaken.
Yes, that's right.
Straw Boy said he only came to Ippel Down to rescue him.
It's insane that he thought to sneak in, and miraculous that he did it.
Um, too bad his plan is dead in the water now.
He has to save himself first, which unfortunately means that he's out of time.
Ace Boy is set to be executed this afternoon at 3 p.m.
I believe they're going to transfer him to Navy Headquarters sometime this morning.
It's already past midnight, so that means Ace Boy will be taken out of Ippel Down in seven or eight hours, tops.
Straw Boy's treatment is going to take two more days to run its course.
And even if he survives, he'll need another three days of recovery to restore his strength.
So by the time he wakes up, it'll all be over.
Are you crazy?
He can't take two more days of that torture.
It's killing him.
As I told you, his chances are extremely low.
We'll need a miracle to make it.
He's not the only one that needs rest.
You had a rough run, too.
Eat something nutritious and go back to bed until you feel like your old self again.
I have a nice, quiet room, just perfect for nappy time.
Screw that!
I'm staying with Straw Boy!
Easy, easy.
There's no need.
There's little hope he'll survive anyway.
It won't do any good.
Oh!
Please, Straw Boy, just...
Hang in there!
I wonder what he's doing back there.
There's not much he can do, is there?
Hang in there!
You can do it, Straw Boy!
I believe in you!
Hang in there!
You can do it!
You've got to be kidding me.
He's been doing that this whole time.
Ha!
Ridiculous!
What's he going to do, yell him back alive?
Come on, let's go.
He'll pass out soon enough.
Hang in there!
So, you're telling me...
You can't even find one little ticletoe!
Look for him again, you simpleton!
No way.
I think he's still back there.
He probably fell asleep right on the ground.
Either that or the moron yelled himself straight into a coma.
I'll go in check!
Yeah, me too.
Just to be sure.
Sounds like Straw Boy's the one doing the yelling.
You know, I bet he went to bed already.
We just didn't notice when he left.
Hang!
Hang in there!
What do you think he's going to accomplish with this madness?
You...
Straw Boy!
He was killing himself!
Hey, are you alright?
This isn't what Straw Hat would want.
Come on, let's help him.
You three keep your hands to yourselves!
Let that man do as he wishes.
But he...
The only way that Bon Boy could show his support is to struggle alongside his friend.
Straw Hat Boy's odds aren't great.
If a cheer can help even the slightest, then he has to try.
And if it can't, at least he won't be alone in his final moments.
Straw Hat Boy!
They've long since passed the limit of human endurance.
Of pain.
But that's what it takes to create a miracle!
For more than 10 hours now, Straw Boy has been suffering, fighting against destiny itself to reclaim his life.
And if he isn't giving up, I won't give up either.
I'll keep cheering to the bitter end!
So, please, hang in there!
Hang in there!
You have to live, Straw Boy!
We believe in you!
Straw Boy!
Hang in there!
We're all over!
Straw Boy!
Hang in there!
WARDEN!
I just heard some strange news from the canteen staff on level five!
Huh?
It's about Straw Hat, sir!
He disappeared!
What?
WARDEN!
V-Vice Warden Henneable!
What in the world are you doing up there?
WARDEN!
V-Vice Warden Henneable!
What in the world are you doing up there?
WARDEN!
What are you doing up there?
You
Listen Ace, that woman, I admit I don't know anything about her
But I think it's safe to assume she's pulling your leg
So what, you're just saying she came all the way down here just to lie to me?
No, sorry, I know you mean well, but honestly, my brother really would break into here
He does stupid things without thinking all the time since we were kids
He's always been reckless and made me worry about him, that idiot
Looks like the day has finally come
Finally is right, I just hope they pull this off without a hitch
That goes without saying, doesn't it? Nobody wants a war in Impel Down
Warden Magellan will be here any minute
Look, what?
What?
The screams
Yes, they've stopped, despite how excruciating the treatment is
I fear his silence brings grim tidings
A true pity, and yeti fought valiantly for over 20 hours
Straw boy
No, how old are you?
Oh
What?
See you later
様々
Meet!
He's still alive!
That can't be right!
It made more sense when he was dead!
The hormone treatment hasn't even gone a day!
Good morning. Warden Magellan, sir.
It's time for the...
Sorry, diarrhea.
Please hurry.
I'm afraid it's time for the transfer of Portkis D. Ace.
Teeth incoming! This way!
It doesn't matter if it's cooked or not, just pile it on!
Hurry up! Just leave it close to him!
Wow, he's taking in food like his stomach's made of quicksand!
I thought this guy was tiny! Where's he put it all?
It's already been 30 minutes and he shows no signs to stopping!
Whoa, look at that! There goes a whole week of food for us!
The boy's got some vitality. I'll give him that!
He's coming out!
He looks like a monster!
Whoa! That's not natural, man!
No!
Wildlife!
Uh-huh.
Oh, better!
Let's go!
After Luffy is miraculously cured by Eva's treatment,
he prepares to set off on his own, hoping to catch up with Ace.
But before he can leave, Eva realizes that Luffy is Dragon's son
and decides to lend a hand, revealing that Eva himself
is a member of the Revolutionary Army.
On the next One Piece, Luffy back in action.
Eva begins the breakout plan.
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!